lstn.net 2014-06-26

# Cloud Provider and Dedicated Server Hosting in Dallas, TX

## Privacy Policy for Limestone Networks, Inc.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at sales@limestonenetworks.com.

At Limestone Networks, Inc., the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by Limestone Networks, Inc. and how it is used.

### Coverage of this Policy

This privacy policy includes limestonenetworks.com, lstn.net and all subdomains within.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, Limestone Networks, Inc. makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Google Analytics

All of the same information recorded in Log Files is also transmitted to Google Analytics. No personally identifying data is included in this type of reporting. You may [ opt out of Google's advertising tracking cookie](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) or [a browser plugin to opt out of all Google Analytics tracking software](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en) if you would like by clicking on the links provided.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

Limestone Networks, Inc. does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

#### Google Advertising

Upon visiting Limestone Networks, Inc. you will receive a tracking cookie from Google which specifies if you are either a current client, current reseller or only a visitor of our site. This cookie is then used on Google's advertising network to provide you with ads relevant to you. 

### Information Sharing

Limestone Networks, Inc. only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Limestone Networks, Inc. in the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.
  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Limestone Networks, Inc., its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If Limestone Networks, Inc. becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### Information Security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to Limestone Networks, Inc. employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes).
